nationallampoon.com 2011-05-24

# Privacy Policy | National Lampoon

We Take Your Privacy Seriously.

This notice describes our privacy policy.

We value the relationship we have with our users and are committed to responsible information-handling practices. We take great care in safeguarding your personal information and exceeding our own internal standards and best practices.  
The website that you are visiting is operated by National Lampoon, Inc. (“NL”). We provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is used at our site. This privacy statement covers the site [www.nationallampoon.com](http://www.nationallampoon.com/).

If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, or complaints arising from our use of your personal information, please contact our Customer Service Department via certified mail to:  
National Lampoon, Inc.  
8228 Sunset Blvd  
Los Angeles, CA 90046  
or via e-mail at [privacypolicy@nationallampoon.com](mailto:privacypolicy@nationallampoon.com).

What Information We Collect and How We Use It

Location Information

Information from IP addresses is used to help administer our Web site, to examine overall traffic trends, and to help us improve our site and make your browsing experience more enjoyable. IP addresses are not linked to any personally identifiable information. IP addressed are additionally used to filter certain advertisements in an effort to show you the most relevant advertisement.

Personally Identifiable Information

Throughout our websites we collect certain types of personally identifiable information including (1) contact information (such as name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number or mobile phone number).  
If you would like to receive registration credentials but are reluctant to provide this information online, you may provide it to us by telephone at (310) 474-5252 during normal PST business hours. We do not knowingly collect information from any person under the age of 18.

We use the contact information you provide to communicate with you. In addition, we use contact information you provide to offer you additional products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you, including newsletters and other information that we or our partners deem to be relevant. You can easily opt out of these correspondence by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of these e-mails.  
Children  
Consistent with the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.  IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE PLEASE LEAVE OUR SITE.  
Supplementation of Information

We may, from time to time, supplement the information we collect online with outside records (e.g., information from our strategic partners, or the United States Postal Service) to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you, and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.  
Sharing of Your Information

Please be assured that any third parties who have access to the information you provide, including our subsidiary sites, partner sites, agents, contractors and business affiliates have agreed to protect it in a manner that is consistent with this privacy policy.

From time to time, we may need to share some of your personally identifiable information with including our subsidiary sites, partner sites, agents, contractors and business affiliates. Also, your shipping information will be shared with a shipping company such as FedEx, for the purposes of delivering your order.

We work closely with trusted third party business affiliates to provide you with information on products and services that may be of interest to you. We may share the contact information you provide with trusted third parties for the purposes of analyzing it to make your customer experience better or for offering products and services to you (advertisers). In addition, you can access NL through many third-party co-branded Web sites. For example, if you see a logo on the page that says “NLHN” or a site that uses the “National Lampoon” mark you are on a co-branded page. Whenever you provide contact information on a co-branded page, that data may be shared with the third-party site through which you access NL. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of such third parties, as this Notice does not cover their use of your information.

Third Party Sharing of Information

NL sometimes may offer content (e.g., promotions, affiliations, sponsorships) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity.  Additionally, if the visitor is registered with NL and participates in such promotions, affiliations or sponsorships their data will be shared with the partner.

Other Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about our visitors when you visit many of our Web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink).  
We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our service pages and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze service usage.

Legal Process/Disclaimer

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, for example, in response to a court order, subpoena or a law enforcement agency’s request.

Choices/Opt Out

If you prefer not to receive marketing information, including emails from us, or wish to fully deactivate your account information from our records if you are no longer an active customer, simply let us know by sending a letter via certified mail to National Lampoon, Inc., c/o Privacy Opt Out, 8228 Sunset Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90046 or via e-mail to [privacypolicy@nationallampoon.com](mailto:privacypolicy@nationallampoon.com).

Cookies

Cookies are used by your computer’s browser to store your preferences. We use both session and persistent cookies. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. It will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. We use cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.  
You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you’ve set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in message boards, forums, polling and surveys  
In addition, some of our business affiliates (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies and their use is not covered by this privacy policy.

Tracking Pixels

This site makes use of a technology designed to enhance your browsing experience. The technology, makes use of a small and transparent Java applet to provide you with a faster browsing experience. In addition, aggregate reporting information is collected and made available to the site owner only. No personal or personally identifiable information is gathered or used for this process.

Links

This site may contain links to other Web sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Our privacy policy does not cover these third parties’ use of information. Visitors should consult the other companies’ and sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this statement, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us by sending a letter to National Lampoon, Inc., c/o Privacy Opt Out, 8228 Sunset Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90046 or via e-mail to [privacypolicy@nationallampoon.com](mailto:privacypolicy@nationallampoon.com).

SMS (Short Messaging Service)

We may use personal information to provide the services you’ve requested, including services that display customized content and advertising.  In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider’s standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence.  You may opt-out and remove your SMS information by sending “STOP”, “END”, “QUIT” to the SMS text message you have received.  If you remove your SMS information from our database it will no longer be used by us for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by us or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you.

Data obtained from you in connection with this SMS service may include your name, address, cell phone number, your provider’s name, and the date, time, and content of your messages.  In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider’s standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence.  All charges are billed by and payable to your mobile service provider.  We will not be liable for any delays in the receipt of any SMS messages, as delivery is subject to effective transmission from your network operator.  SMS message services are provided on an AS IS basis.

We may use personal information to provide the services you’ve requested, including services that display customized content and advertising.  We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve our technologies and services.  We may share aggregated and non personal information with third parties outside of NL. When we use third parties to assist us in processing your personal information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.  We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.

You may remove your information from our database. If you remove your information from our database it will no longer be used by us for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by us or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you. You may remove your information by sending your request in writing via email to [privacypolicy@nationallampoon.com](mailto:privacypolicy@nationallampoon.com) or by sending “STOP”, “END”, “QUIT” to the SMS text message you have received or by writing our Customer Service Department via mail to National Lampoon, Inc., 8228 Sunset Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90046.

Updates and Notification of Changes

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Notice. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this notice so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. If we make any material changes in our privacy practices that affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change for a minimum of 30 days.  
By visiting this web site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
